I'm wearing with larger documents you
may wish to insert page numbers the date
a company logo or other information into
a section of the letter or document if
you wanted to appear on all pages you
would primarily use the headers and
footers tool for this to access the
headers and footers tool if you go to
the insert tab and move your mouse along
you will see the header drop down now
there are a range of pre formatted
templates for the headers or footers but
if you just wish to edit a blank header
or footer you would just simply go down
at the bottom and click Edit header in
this example I'm just going to insert a
date and as you can see know that I'm in
the head on footer it's indicated that
as a dotted Lane it's in the heading
section if I move down the page you can
see it's indicated that they thought I
was there and again it's indicated that
this section here and this section here
will be the header and footer so I'm
simply going to insert the did I've
selected the attaint the option of want
to select is that one and click block
here so that is inserted into the header
now as you can see it is nice and clear
there but if I click away from that it
goes slightly Korean no that means I
can't edit it to actually get into the
header and footer again as a quicker
we're then going to the insert if I just
double click alongside it it will
automatically open up the header or the
footer I now also wish to add a pH
numbers to the documents footer so if I
go down to the footer again that's a
blank footer or I can just click Edit
footer there are templates they're
available different ways it could be
formatted simply you want to go to edit
footer and in there I want to select
page number and it's going to be a clean
number that is ended up there so if I
double click away from that I can now
see that the page number is in the
bottom and the D is in the header if I
was taping in this document and I went
on to page two if I just press the Enter
key to take me down to a new page as you
can see every page
it is adding the teeth and a new pH
number